{
    "subject": "Marco_Ferreri",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Conjugal_Bed",
    "human_readable": "Marco Ferreri directed the film The Conjugal Bed.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.913250207901001,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Marco Ferreri."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8973833918571472,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8843323588371277,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Conjugal Bed'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7410922050476074,
            "question": "Are there any other notable films directed by Marco Ferreri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6336642503738403,
            "question": "Is 'The Conjugal Bed' a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5282080769538879,
            "question": "Where might one find information about the film 'The Conjugal Bed'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4648072421550751,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Marco Ferreri's filmography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4641094207763672,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in the film 'The Conjugal Bed'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39176109433174133,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Conjugal Bed' likely to belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3425696790218353,
            "question": "What kind of work did Marco Ferreri create?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marco Ferreri directed the film The Conjugal Bed.",
            "html": "yago_8383_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'The Conjugal Bed' likely to belong to?",
            "html": "yago_8383_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes might be explored in the film 'The Conjugal Bed'?",
            "html": "yago_8383_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Marco Ferreri's filmography?",
            "html": "yago_8383_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_8383_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents confirm that Marco Ferreri directed \"The Conjugal Bed,\" which was released in 1963. Therefore, the statement \"Marco Ferreri directed the film The Conjugal Bed\" is supported by the information given."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}